omnihotels.com 2019-07-15

# Privacy Policy | Omni Hotels & Resorts

## We don’t share your private information

This policy was last updated on May 24, 2018.

Omni Hotels & Resorts® respects the privacy of all our guests, and we are committed to protecting it. This policy describes how we collect, use, and disclose information about our guests.

### INFORMATION COLLECTED

We collect information that can identify you personally, such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, etc. (“personal data”) only when it is voluntarily provided to us by you or by a third party (such as a travel agency) on your behalf. We collect personal data when it is provided through forms on our websites, mobile applications, over the phone, through physical mail or e-mail, or in-person.

This website does not collect, save or store any personal data from you while you simply browse this website, unless you voluntarily and intentionally provide it to us (for example, by making an online booking or requesting further information).

Our servers automatically collect certain technical, non-personal information when you use our websites or mobile applications (“usage data”). Technical data may include your browser type, operating system, page views and clicks, IP address, unique device ID, and referral URLs.

### USE OF INFORMATION

We use your personal data to fulfill the purpose for which it was provided, or as otherwise set forth in this policy. For example, we may use your personal data as necessary to:

  * process your reservation request and payment;
  * enroll you in Omni Hotels Select Guest® or the DISCOVERY guest loyalty program;
  * contact you about your reservation;
  * make requested changes to your reservation or user account;
  * provide you with a personalized experience on our websites;
  * respond to your inquiries and other communications;
  * register you to receive newsletters or other information for which you’ve expressed an interest; and
  * to comply with legal requirements.

You may opt out of receiving any promotional or marketing emails at any time by contacting us directly or by following the “opt out” or “unsubscribe” links in such emails. We may, however, continue to contact you with relevant information about your past or upcoming reservations with us.

We may use the usage data we collect for any reason we deem appropriate, including to improve, maintain, and operate our websites and services.

### SHARING OF INFORMATION

We will not sell any of your personal data to any outside organization. We only disclose your personal data to third parties as reasonably necessary to carry out the permitted uses described in the “USE OF INFORMATION” section of this policy. For example, we may share personal data with:

  * ·our payment processors, technical and customer support contractors, and other service providers who are required to keep the personal data confidential and are prohibited from using it other than to carry out their services on our behalf;
  * ·our successors in the event of a sale, merger, acquisition, or similar transaction affecting the relevant portion of our business; and
  * legal and governmental authorities or other third parties, to the extent required to comply with a legal order or applicable law.

### SECURITY OF PERSONAL DATA

Omni Hotels & Resorts is committed to the security of your personal data. We use commercially reasonable technical measures to protect personal data in our possession, and our website uses secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology to help protect the privacy of credit card information, name, address, email and other sensitive information you provide to us.

### COOKIES AND PROFILES

Omni Hotels & Resorts and our third party marketing partners may use cookies, invisible pixels, local shared objects (i.e., persistent cookies) and web beacons to obtain information about visitors of our websites and mobile applications. Cookies are small text files that are placed on a computer or mobile device when you visit a website or use an app. We use cookies on our websites and apps to personalize content presented to you, retain information such as dates and room selection as you proceed through the reservation process, allow you to sign in more easily, and track responses to our ads.

You can set your computer to warn you each time a cookie is sent or turn off all cookies (except Flash cookies) through your browser. Check your browser's Help menu or your built-in mobile device settings to find out how. Some mobile devices store cookies not only in areas connected to the browser, but also in areas that are app-specific, which cannot be controlled by the browser settings. Check your app settings options on your mobile device to find out how to manage or delete cookies that may be stored in these other areas. If you do not accept cookies, some features, services or activities that are available on our websites or mobile apps may be adversely affected and you may be unable to perform certain transactions, use certain functionality, and access certain content. The choice to accept or deny a cookie is different from your choice to accept/deny email messages.

We also serve ads through third-party advertising technology. In the course of serving our advertisements to you, unique third-party persistent cookies, clear gifs or beacon gifs may be placed on your computer or device to help manage our online advertising, recognize when a device visits our websites, learn which ads bring users to our websites, and track whether a reservation is made. The information our ad-serving providers and we collect through this technology is not personally identifiable but is used to create an anonymous profile which allows the ad-serving provider to serve ads targeted towards you and your interests across the ad-serving network.  Our third party marketing partners may then pool the anonymous information that they collect from our websites and mobile applications with other sources of information, which may include your name and mailing address, for purposes of sending you direct mail or a catalog.

Our websites do not currently respond to “Do Not Track” signals that may be sent by your device or browser.

### LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEB SITES

Please be aware that third-party websites available through links on our websites each have separate privacy and data collection practices. We have no control, responsibility or liability for these third-party websites or their applicable policies or content. Omni Hotels & Resorts cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you disclose on third-party sites.

### INFORMATION FOR EUROPEAN/SWISS CITIZENS

We comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield  Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data transferred from the European Union and/or Switzerland to the United States. We have certified to the Department of Commerce that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, we will resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal data. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this policy should first contact us as set forth at the bottom of this policy. We also commit to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and/or the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner, and comply with the advice given by the panel and/or Commissioner, with regard to personal data transferred from the EU and/or Switzerland. EU and Swiss residents may, under certain conditions, invoke binding arbitration for complaints regarding Privacy Shield compliance not resolved by any of the other Privacy Shield mechanisms. For more information, see Annex I: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction>.

We may be liable for onward transfers of personal data from the EU or Switzerland to third parties. The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over our compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles.

**Data Controller** : We are typically the data controller, as that term is used in applicable European privacy laws, for any personal data that we collect from you. However, when we collect personal data about you from a third party (e.g., travel agencies), the third party may be the data collector for such data and we may be the data processor. If we are acting as the data processor, we will only process the relevant personal data as requested by the data controller.

**Retention** : We may retain your personal data so long as we can reasonably foresee the data may be required in connection with our relationship with you (for example, to address inquiries regarding past or future reservations, or so long as you maintain a user account with us), or as required by law.

**Access, Correction, Deletion** : You may access and correct your personal data that we process, except where the burden of providing you such access would be disproportionate to the risks to your privacy, or where the rights of other persons would be violated. You may also request erasure of your personal data in certain circumstances. To request access to, correction of, or erasure of your personal data, please contact us as set forth at the end of this privacy policy. In cases where we are not the data controller (such as when the personal data was collected from or on behalf of an air travel provider or other customer), we may need to refer you or your request to the applicable data controller instead.

### CHILDREN’S POLICY

Our websites and services are not intended for children and we do not knowingly solicit or collect personal data from children. If we are notified or discover that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personal data to us, we will take reasonable steps to delete the information. We do present information regarding Omni Sensational Kids program on our websites for the reference of adults that are interested in activities at our locations for children.

### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

We may update this policy from time to time. We will always post the then-current version of this policy on our websites, and will indicate at the top of the policy the date on which the latest version took effect. Please review this policy from time to time to stay updated on our privacy practices.

### CONTACT

If you have any questions about this policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at:

Mail:  4001 Maple Avenue, Suite 600

Dallas, Texas, 75219

Attention: Legal Department

E-Mail: privacy@omnihotels.com

Phone: +1 800 809 6664
